





WHO AM I?

I am an Artificial Intelligence MSc graduate with experience in working with Deep Learning, Computer Vision, and Time Series Analysis in the medical domain.

My goal is to help you apply machine learning solutions to important problems, and to know when that is the right choice.

SKILLS

Pytorch (Lightning) · Tensorboard · Slurm · Pandas · scikit-learn · pytest · gRPC · H5PY · OpenSlide · Docker · Singularity

EXPERIENCE

11/2021 - Now **Deep Learning Researcher**

Medis Medical Imaging I researched, developed, and validated production-ready computer vision algorithms (Deep Learning-based and otherwise) for echocardiography workflow automation, and maintained and developed inference and evaluation infrastructure.

Pytorch (Lightning) · Slurm · scikit-learn · pytest · gRPC · Docker

5/2021-7/2021 **Artificial Intelligence Analyst** The Netherlands Cancer Institute

The Netherlands Cancer Institute

KPN

I investigated Deep Learning-based methods for outcome prediction of Ductal Carcinoma in Situ (DCIS) from pathology whole-slide images (WSIs).

Pytorch · Slurm · Docker · Singularity

11/2019 - 4/2021

internship

Research Intern

Researched and developed a computational pipeline for predicting outcome of DCIS from WSIs. Pytorch · Slurm · Docker · Singularity

6/2019 Research Intern internship NLP and Data Mining project in collaboration with the University of Amsterdam.

scikit-learn

3/2018 - 6/2018

3/2018 - 8/2018

Teaching Assistant I assisted teaching for the BSc Neural Networks course at the University of Groningen.

Universitair Medisch Centrum Groningen I analysed biometric signals to perform early detection of sepsis in ICU patients.

scikit-learn

EDUCATION

2018 - 2021 MSc in Artificial Intelligence (Cum Laude) **University of Amsterdam**

University of Groningen

I presented an abstract on my thesis Multiple-Instance Learning for Assessing Prognosis of Ductal Carcinoma In Situ at the European Congress of Pathology of 2021. Follow-up research based on my work was accepted at SPIE 2022.

Python

2015 - 2018

BSc in Artificial Intelligence (Honours in Philosophy)

University of Groningen

I presented a paper resulting from my thesis on Early Detection of Sepsis Induced Deterioration Using Machine Learning at the BENELEARN2018 conference, and the paper was published in the conference proceedings.

Python · C · Matlab · Java

SOFT SKILLS **LANGUAGES HOBBIES**

I am organized, detail oriented, and strong at team building, communication, and presentation.

English - C2 Italian - C2

I love cooking, playing bass, sailing, and kung fu.